korg.com 2010-12-30

# Korg - Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**  
KORG USA Inc. understands your concerns about privacy and we treat your personal information as confidential. We do not rent, sell, barter or trade e-mail addresses. When you place an order with us, we collect your name, address, telephone number, credit card information and your e-mail address. We use this information to fulfill your order and to communicate with you about your order. We may use this information to communicate additional information about this website.

**How to Contact Us**  
If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy or would like to obtain a copy of our 30-day Satisfaction Guarantee, you may contact us using the above contact information, Attention Legal Department.

**Collection of Information**  
_Registration and Use of Information_  
No user is required to provide information in order to visit korg.com. However, a user must register in order to be placed on our e-mail distribution list. In addition, a user must register to enter contests and other promotions. During registration, a user provides certain categories of information, such as his or her name, address and e-mail address. We also collect information regarding a user's registered products. The information which you supply us enables us to customize our website to your interests and enhance your overall experience at our website. In addition, it helps us communicate with you about KORG product news. Besides sending you e-mail updates, we may use your contact information periodically in order to send you e-mail regarding upcoming events and promotions. In addition, we may request information for other specific purposes. If the information provided will be used in any way that differs from the treatment outlined in this Privacy Policy, we will identify the differences when we request the information.

The  korg.com website contains links to websites operated by third parties. These websites may collect personally identifiable information about you. This Privacy Policy does not cover third-party data collection practices and KORG USA Inc. does not assume any responsibility for third parties. Please check the privacy policy at each website you visit.

If Korg USA, Inc. were to be acquired, personal information about our customers might be one of the assets acquired.

_Passive Collection of Information_  
In addition to the information that you actively provide to us, such as the information you provide when you register for our e-mail updates, we collect information about how you interact with our website. We collect such passive information for purposes such as testing and improving a user's experience at the website and for compiling broad aggregate demographic data and related usage data for our internal purposes. The types of passive information include, but are not limited to, your IP address, which type of browser you are using, where you go on our website and how long you stay on any part of our website. We may also track how you interact with our website, by assigning a random string of numbers and characters to your session. Passive information does not identify you to us by name, and we do not link your IP address to your personally identifiable information.

We use a "cookie" based data collection system in certain areas of our website. Cookies are small files placed on your hard drive that assist us in providing customized services; for example, the use of cookies allows us to reduce the frequency with which you will need to enter your password on password-protected areas of our website. Additionally, in some cases, certain website features will only function with the use of a cookie. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, although in that case you may not be able to use certain features on our website and/or you may be required to reenter your password more frequently during a session.

_Collection of Information from Children_  
KORG USA Inc. abides by federal law and the guidelines of the Federal Trade Commission regarding youth privacy. As such, this website is directed to the general public. We do not knowingly collect information from children under 13.

_Sharing of Information_  
KORG USA Inc. pledges that it will not sell, share, rent or otherwise transfer your information. We may however share broad aggregate demographic data and related usage information with our business partners. This aggregate information does not contain any personal information which can identify any individual user.

While we strive to protect the personal information of our users, we will release personal information if required by law or if, in good faith, we believe such action is necessary.

**Other Provisions**  
_Acceptance of Terms/Changes to Privacy Policy_  
Your use of this website indicates an acceptance of the terms of the Privacy Policy, and other Terms of Use in effect at the time of such usage. KORG USA Inc. reserves the right to update or amend this Privacy Policy at any time.

If we are going to use your personally identifiable information in a manner which materially differs from the standards in effect at the time such information was collected, we will notify you and you will have a choice as to whether or not we use your information in this different manner. If you have provided information to receive from us, our e-mail updates and other commercial e-mail, you will be contacted by us, via e-mail, regarding this materially different use. In addition, if we make any material changes to our Privacy Policy that do not affect user information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our website notifying users that our Privacy Policy has changed. In some cases when we post such a notice, we will also send an e-mail to users who have provided their information notifying them of the changes in our Privacy Policy.

_Choice/Opt-out_  
Korg.com users are asked to give information to be put on the KORG USA e-mail distribution list or to receive commercial e-mail regarding upcoming promotions and events. If you receive our commercial e-mail and would like to avoid receiving such e-mail in the future, you may opt-out of receiving it by following the opt-out directions provided within the e-mail. We will only communicate with you according to your instructions.

Your privacy is important to KORG USA Inc. If you have questions about any of the provisions described above, please contact us at using the contact information listed above.
